If you have a sick bird, there are several things to remember.
But the first and foremost is to get that bird isolated, away from all your other birds as fast as possible.
Then the bird needs warmth.
Use a heating pad, a brooder, anything that you can to get warmth to that bird.
I would suggest highly that when you know a bird is sick, that you see a, an avian vet.
They're not a lot of avian vets around, but there are many good ones around.
The reason being, that a bird does not show that it is sick, until it is well sick.
Because, they are attuned to hiding any illness away from their flock so that they won't be banned from the flock.
So, by the time you can see that a bird is sick, it has been sick for a while.
I use Marvel Aid if a bird is just being stressed.
Say, from moving it from one location to another.
Marvel Aid works real well for minor things.
But there is nothing that can beat the intelligence and knowledge of an avian vet when you have a sick bird.
And more than likely, that will be the only way you'll be able to save that bird.
If your bird has been exposed to smoke, near a fire or anywhere where the smoke has got to the bird, birds cannot get that smoke out of their lungs.
They may go on for months and never show a sign, and then all of the sudden, you loose that bird.
Fires are very dangerous to birds, and, I myself even had a fire in which I thought my birds were fine, and then months later I started loosing them, and it was said that it was due to the smoke in their lung.